dailyworth.com 2019-04-02

# Privacy Policy | HerMoney

## **PRIVACY POLICY**

Last Revised: September 21, 2018

Her Money respects your privacy and we are committed to protecting it through our compliance with this policy.

HerMoney Media, Inc. (“us”, “we”, or “our”) operates the HerMoney.com website (the “Service”).  
  
This privacy policy (“Privacy Policy”) describes how information and data is collected from you when you use this online website, mobile website, digital service, or any related products, services, sites, features or functionality, including when you sign-up for our newsletters (each a “Service”, collectively the “Services”) and how HerMoney, uses, shares and manages your information and data.

By using any of the Services, you consent to the collection, use, processing, and sharing of your information as described in this Privacy Policy. Each time you visit the Website or use the services, you agree and expressly consent to our collection, use, and disclosure of the information that you provide as described in this policy. BY ACCESSING THE SITE, UTILIZING ANY OF THE SERVICES AND/OR REGISTERING WITH US, YOU ACKNOWLEDGE THAT YOU HAVE READ, UNDERSTOOD AND AGREE TO BE BOUND BY THIS POLICY, INCLUDING OUR TERMS OF SERVICE, WHICH ARE INCORPORATED HEREIN BY REFERENCE.

## **Types of Information Collected**

### Personal Information

HerMoney may ask you for some or all of the following types of information which may be identifiable to you when you register for our App or Services, access various content or features, or directly contact the site: (i) contact information, including your email address and name; (ii) your age; (iii) demographic information such as zip code, preferences, and interests and (iv)other information relevant to customer surveys and/or offers; (v) information for the purpose of authenticating yourself or your account if we have reason to believe, in our sole discretion, that you may be violating site policies or for any other reason we deem necessary (collectively “Personal Information”). You are responsible for ensuring the accuracy of all Personal Information you submit to HerMoney.

We also collect and store the Personal Information you voluntarily submit to us through registering with us or uploading or posting User Content through the Site or Services. If you are signed into your social media account(s) such as Tumblr, Twitter, pinterest, instagram, linkedin or Facebook account and you “like” or “comment” on HerMoney Content (such as the articles found on our blog) or other User Content, your social media username will be displayed and so available to the public. You agree that your username, likes, feedback, and any associated comments may become public information; we therefore urge you to exercise caution when deciding to disclose any Personal Information on the Site, the App or through the Services.

In addition, if you choose to purchase or subscribe to a feature or Services of HerMoney that requires a Fee, you will be required to provide us with your billing information, including, without limitation, bank account numbers, credit card or debit card numbers, account details, ACH information, and similar data (collectively, “Billing Information”).

### Non-Personal Information

Cookies and Other Technologies. We may utilize cookies and other technologies, such as, web beacons (also known as “clear gifs” and “pixel tags”) to recognize you, customize your experience, and serve advertisements. Cookies are very small files placed on your computer, and they allow us to count the number of visitors to HerMoney and distinguish repeat visitors from new visitors. They also allow us to save User preferences and track User trends. We may also enable advertisers and ad servers to promote third party products and/or services by placing advertisements on HerMoney. These advertisers and ad servers may use cookies and/or web beacons to monitor information related to served advertisements. 

Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website, by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us.  
This information allows ad networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This Policy covers the use of cookies by HerMoney and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers. You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website.  

Information Collected Automatically. We automatically receive and collect information such as your IP address, the URLs of websites you arrive at HerMoney from or leave HerMoney to go to, your type of browser and language, access times, the content of any undeleted cookies that your browser previously accepted from us, your operating system, your mobile provider, your mobile device, and your ISP. We may use such information to better understand how HerMoney visitors use the Site and the App, to analyze trends, administer the website, prevent fraud, and gather broad demographic information.

### Our Use of Your Information

Our primary purpose in collecting information, both Personal Information and other, is to provide you with a safe, smooth, efficient, and customized experience. You agree that we may use your information to: provide the Services and customer support you request; troubleshoot problems and prevent potentially prohibited or illegal activities; customize, measure and improve our Site, the App, our Services, content and advertising; tell you about and administer our Site, App or Services, targeted marketing, service updates, contests, sweepstakes, rewards, and promotional offers based on your communication preferences; monitor and enforce our Terms of Service; communicate with Users about products and/or services you may be interested in; verify your eligibility to use the Site or the App.

### Contests, Promotions, Simulations or Games

From time to time, HerMoney may offer as part of the Services, or through the Web Site, contests, promotions, games, or simulations (collectively, “Contests”). To participate in Contests, subscribers may be required to complete a registration form; participation is not allowed  in any jurisdiction where such Contest is not permitted under applicable law. Upon submission, all registrations become the exclusive property of HerMoney. Registered users (each, a “Registered User”) are permitted only one account. Registered Users with more than one account are subject to immediate disqualification from any Contest, unless the description of the Contest expressly invites a user to register multiple times. HerMoney, at its sole discretion, may suspend or revoke the registration of any Registered User.

Registered Users agree to release HerMoney and its agents, advertisers, sponsors or promotional partners, from all liability arising from participation in any Contest located on, or accessed through, the Web Site. HerMoney is not responsible for technical, hardware or software failures of any kind, lost or unavailable network connections, or failed, incomplete, garbled or delayed computer transmissions which may limit any Registered User’s ability to participate in any Game.

Each Registered User agrees to be bound by the rules of any Contest and by the rules of fair play and consideration of fellow Registered User. A Registered User who violates any of the rules or guidelines for behavior published on the Web Site, or the site where the Contest is conducted, are subject to immediate disqualification and revocation of their registration. HerMoney is under no obligation to award any prize to any Registered User who violates a published rule or guideline.

Some Contest may offer prizes to Registered Users. All prizes are subject to the official game or contest rules published with that Contest.

HerMoney reserves the right to cancel, terminate or alter any Contest or the rules thereof at any time without prior notification.

### Our Disclosure of Your Information

HerMoney is committed to maintaining your trust and we want you to understand when and with whom we may share information collected about you. We may disclose Personal Information, Billing Information and Non-Personal Information to respond to legal requirements, enforce our policies, respond to claims that a listing or other content violates the rights of others, or protect anyone’s rights, property, or safety. Such information will be disclosed in accordance with applicable laws and regulations.

We may also use and/or share your Personal Information, Billing Information and Non-Personal Information with, and you authorize us to use and/or share this information with:

–   Service providers under contract who help with our business operations. We employ these companies and people to perform tasks on our behalf and need to share your information with them to provide products and services to you.

–   We will share your Billing Information with a third party service provider as necessary to process your payments. The third party service provider stores your Billing Information; we do not store this information. Storage by the third party service provider of your Billing Information is subject to the privacy policies and practices of the third party service provider and is not subject to the terms of this privacy policy. By providing your Billing Information, you acknowledge and agree to use of such information by the third party service provider for purposes of processing your payment to us.

–   Certain of HerMoney’s program participants under confidentiality agreement, as we in our sole discretion believe necessary or appropriate in connection with an investigation of fraud, intellectual property infringement, piracy, or other unlawful activity.

–   Our affiliates and promotional partners, so they can offer you special products, services, discounts, tickets, and other items or services.  Likewise, we may receive information from such affiliates and promotional partners to offer our Users special items or services.

–   We may combine your information with information we collect from other companies and use it to improve and personalize our services, content and advertising.

–   We may sell or rent your information to third parties for marketing purposes without your explicit consent, if permitted by law.

–   In an ongoing effort to better understand our Users, we may analyze certain Non-Personal Information in anonymized and aggregate form in order to operate, maintain, manage, and improve the Site, the App, the Services and/or such products and services.  This aggregate information does not identify you personally. We may share and/or license this aggregate data to our affiliates, agents, business and promotional partners and other third parties. We may also disclose aggregated user statistics in order to describe the Services and these products and services to current and prospective business partners and to other third parties for other lawful purposes.

–   We may share some or all of your Information with any of our parent companies, subsidiaries, joint ventures, or other companies under common control with us. Including but not limited to Her Money Media, Inc., and Samuel Bennett, Inc. and affiliates.

–   As we develop our businesses, we might sell or buy businesses or assets.  In the event of a corporate sale, merger, reorganization, sale of assets, dissolution, or similar event, the Information may be part of the transferred assets.

### Disclosure for Law Enforcement:

Under certain circumstances, We may be required to disclose your Personal Data if required to do so by law or in response to valid requests by public authorities (e.g. a court or a government agency).  
We. may disclose your Personal Data in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: comply with a legal obligation;protect and defend the rights of our property, to prevent or investigate possible wrongdoing in connection with the Service; to protect the personal safety of users of the Service or the public.

If you do not wish to receive marketing communications from us or participate in our ad-customization programs, simply indicate your preference or by following the directions provided with the communication or advertisement.

### No Spam or Spyware

We do not tolerate spam. Spamming is explicitly prohibited it by our Terms of Service. If you would like to report an incident of spamming or other unauthorized communications from other Users, please contact us at privacy@HerMoney.com. We maintain the right to investigate such incidents and take suitable action.

### Account Protection

We take commercially reasonable steps to protect your information from loss, misuse, and unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration, or destruction. Nevertheless, no transmission over the Internet and no data storage method can be guaranteed to be safe 100% of the time. HerMoney cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to HerMoney or guarantee that your end user data stored on the App or the Services may not be accessed, disclosed, altered, or destroyed by breach of any of our industry standard physical, technical, or managerial safeguards.  In particular, e-mail sent to us may not be secure, and you should therefore take special care in deciding what information you send to us via email.

Our Sites are operated and maintained within the U.S. We make no assurances or representations of any kind that the Sites are suitable for use outside the U.S. or in the country in which you reside.  Accordingly, if you are located outside of the United States, any information you provide to us will be transferred to the United States. By providing us with any information, you consent to its transfer and storage in the United States. 

We. will retain your Personal Data only for as long as is necessary for the purposes set out in this Privacy Policy. We will retain and use your Personal Data to the extent necessary to comply with our legal obligations (i.e. if we are required to retain your data to comply with applicable laws), resolve disputes, and enforce our legal agreements and policies.  
In addition, HerMoney does not monitor, recognize, or honor any opt-out or do not track mechanisms, including general web browser “Do Not Track” settings and/or signals.

### Email Communications

We may use your email to deliver HerMoney and our affiliates newsletter(s), as well as for other promotional (e.g., new product offerings, special offers by us or other third parties) purposes. Email messages we send you may contain code that enables our database to track your usage of the emails we send you, such usage includes whether the email was opened and what links (if any) were clicked. If you send an email to us, or fill out our “Feedback” form, we will collect your email address and the full content of your email, including attached files, and other information you provide.

You may indicate your preference to opt out of receiving promotional communications by following the unsubscribe instructions provided in the promotional email you receive or by contacting us directly at privacy@HerMoney.com. You acknowledge that it may take up to 10 days for us to process an opt-out request. Please note, however, that you cannot opt out of receiving transactional emails related to your account with us.

### Third Parties

Except as otherwise expressly included in this Policy, this document addresses only the use and disclosure of information we collect from you. If you disclose your information to others Users on our Site or on other sites throughout the internet, different rules may apply to their use or disclosure of the information you disclose to them. We do not control the privacy policies of third parties, and you are subject to the privacy policies of those third parties where applicable. We are not responsible for any information we do not collect. We encourage you to ask questions before you disclose your Personal Information to others.

### Children

Protecting the privacy of young children is especially important to us. For that reason, HerMoney does not knowingly collect or solicit Personal Information from anyone under the age of 13. If you are under 13, please do not give us any Personal Information.  We encourage parents and legal guardians to monitor their children’s Internet usage and to help enforce our Privacy Policy by instructing their children never to provide Personal Information through the Site or the App without their permission. If you have reason to believe that a child under the age of 13 has provided Personal Information to us, please contact us, and we will endeavor to delete that information from our databases.

### Ownership

Her Money Media, Inc., its subsidiaries, affiliated companies, distributors, vendors, independent contractors, partners, and/or licensors (collectively, the “SBI Parties“) are the owners or licensees of all content and materials on the Site (“Site Content“) and of all related intellectual property rights, including, without limitation, all copyrights, moral rights, trademark rights and patent rights.  Site Content includes, without limitation, all features, functions, services, software, algorithms, designs, objects, documentation, know-how, code, data, art, graphics, animation, photographs, images, text, music, sound effects, audio and/or audio-visual elements, and downloadable materials on the Site, as well as the look-and-feel, design, layout, organization, presentation, user interface, navigation and stylistic conventions of the Site.  You do not acquire any ownership interests in any Site Content by accessing, browsing or otherwise using the Site.  

### Intellectual Property Rights

All materials contained in this Web Site are the copyrighted property of HerMoney and its affiliates or licensors. As between HerMoney and you, HerMoney is the sole owner of all content on the Web Site, including without limitation, all applicable U.S. and non-U.S. copyrights, patents, trademarks, and trade secrets, and other intellectual property rights thereto. Except as otherwise specifically provided in these Terms and Conditions, you may not download or save a copy of the Web Site or any portion thereof, for any purpose. You may, however, print a copy of individual screens appearing as part of the Web Site solely for your personal, non-commercial use or records, provided that any marks, logos or other legends that appear on the copied screens remain on, and are not removed from the printed or stored images of such screens. All title and intellectual property rights in and to the content of the Linked Sites is the property of the respective content owner and may be protected by applicable copyright or other intellectual property laws and treaties.  
  
California Privacy Rights

Under California Civil Code Sections 1798.83-1798.84, you are entitled to request a notice identifying the categories of personal information which we share with third parties for marketing purposes, and providing contact information for such third parties. If you are a California resident and would like this information, send us an email at privacy@HerMoney.com with “California Privacy Rights” in the subject line or write us at HerMoney, 72 N State Road, Suite 156 Briarcliff Manor NY 10510-1414.

### Changes to this Policy

We reserve the right, at any time, to add to, change, update, or modify this Policy. Any such changes to this Policy will be posted here on our Site so we urge to please visit this page frequently. In all cases, use of information we collect is subject to the Policy in effect at the time such information is collected. Please refer back to this Privacy Policy on a regular basis.

### How to Contact Us

If you wish to request a copy of or make updates to your personal information collected by HerMoney, please contact us at privacy@HerMoney.com.

Copyright © 2018 HerMoney, Inc. All Rights Reserved.
